[{"answer": "Where'd you meet her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "On an elevator? You met a woman on an elevator", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Wow", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What did she say?", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No, about the nose job", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Well, I've thought about it, but I don't know", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "We have time", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "It is exciting", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well, I'm sure they'll be able to fix it. You can't stop modern science. Can't stop it, you can't stop it. Can't stop science. Can't be stopped, no way, no how, science just marche", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Shut up", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I told you, I threw it out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You told me not to give it to you, you made me promise", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, I changed my mind, I want that number", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I was lying, give it to me", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "We did", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What do I need this for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We're engaged", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh, hello Miss Pepper, it's a pleasure to meet you.  And you must be Professor my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I've read your book, Professor, and I was quite intrigued by it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Tell me, is it your contention that my friend was an imposter", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yes, your contention", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "My contention", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yes, that's my contention", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Oh, it was a fram", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Oh, well, we're all proud of the work I'm doing", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah, pretty much. my friend shows off the fruits of their labo", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nose-Job.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 28}]